(818) 395-5632 jenny.wannier@gmail.com https://alathea23.github.io/ /React-Portfolio/

Professional Summary

Full-Stack Developer &
Experienced Project Manager
(\$1 mil budget)

- Concurrently responsible for operations & events
- Strong relationship building and **C-Suite level reporting**
- Financial analytics, editing/ technical content management
- Sales account management,B2B, & customer relations

Self-starting, effective and deft team player who enjoys analysis & challenge.

 SaaS product building, QA, technical writing and general technical aptitude.

Certifications

Certified Full-Stack Web
Developer - UCLA (Dec. '23)
PMP Certification (In Progress)

Skills

Jira, Git, Confluence, Notion (Agile methodologies) Javascript (NodeJS, MongoDB, ReactJS, jQuery, MERN stack) Sql (MySQL, NoSQL) HTML, CSS, Heroku Technical Writing (Markdown) QA Testing/Technical Review Metadata Maintenance OpenBOM/BOM management Sales Analysis/Optimization Inventory/Supply Chain Management Edelweiss, Anthology, Bookstat Expert Excel/Google Sheets Expert Office/Google Suite Expert Adobe **CRM & Salesforce** Proficient German Strong writing &

communication skills

Jenny Wannier Tarzian

Education

University of Colorado at Boulder (2006-2009)

- Spent final 3 years in BA program with honor status (B.S. Biochemistry).

UCLA - Full-Stack Web Developer Certification (2023)

- Diverse full-stack web portfolio, affinity for Sequel databases (back) & ReactJS (front)

Work History

Camino Robotics: Project Manager (contract)

2023 – *Present*

- Oversee updates on technical mechanical engineering design; run detailed QA.
- Drafted technical documentation including build instructions and testing protocols.
- Coordinate workflow (w/ Jira) between engineering contractor teams & internal team.
- On-site inventory management incl. software set-up, BOM maintenance, & procedures.
- Facilitate purchasing, vendor/product research ensuring ISO compliant components.
- Scope, organize, & manage FDA medical product testing and certification process.

Zibby's Bookshop: Store Launch - Manager

2022 - 2023

- Establish & implement store opening including **retail & inventory systems**, customer engagement, staffing, purchasing, receiving & stock, & event operations.
- Stewardship of metadata system, accurate COG, sales tracking & analysis, etc.
- Reduced initial inventory costs by 9% from conventional stocking procedures; establish all vendor accounts & terms, optimized inventory discounts w/ delivery.
- Developed all store procedures in tandem with training/on-boarding staff of 10
- Early analysis of market needs. Recommend sales strategy/inventory adjustments.
- Oversaw website design/computer integration, audit consistency & reproducibility.

Various Labs: Data Manager - Intermittent

2012 - 2023

- Collated, organized and ran basic analysis of raw data for epidemiology labs.
- Performed editorial review for technical and mathematical research papers.

Nolo: Associate Operations Manager

2022

- Designed **SaaS** product, operational flow, metadata structure, & support resources for DIY legal filing product, reporting to C-Suite on deadlines, progress, & targets.
- Drafted and oversaw coding updates for consumer portal, including **QA** process.
- Synthesized research & data to optimize product/procedures and identify issues.
- Helped create and maintain database structure and reference; legal compliancy.
- Managed and trained project researchers, overseeing workflow and work quality.
- Trained and supported CS through updates and new product launches.

Flintridge Bookstore: 2007 – 2022 (Concurrent Managerial Positions): General Buyer/Inventory Manager 2016 – 2022

- Increased children's sales 11% in tough market, streamlined buying procedures.
- Integrated & automated buying to receiving process; oversaw receiving/returns.
- Detailed sales analysis for trends/category performance including sales forecast.
- Managed & operated all B2B & off-site fair/author events, increased sales 30% through new partnerships; maintained off-site hardware, software & procedures
- Managed **high-level customer interface**, strong customer satisfaction.
- Strategic sourcing to reduce inventory costs by 7.5% while maintaining availability.
- Managed all supplier orders and accounts, 120-150 rotating vendors, 1m budget.
- Organized & managed in-store events w/ marketing manager; 75-400+ attendees.
- Created and updated store website, Designed monthly ¼ page print news ad

Children's Buyer & Specialist; Inventory Manager

2015 – April 2022

- Managed inventory and displays for the children's, toys/gift, and game sections
- Coordinated B2B, core literature, & giveback programs with schools.

On-Demand Publishing Manager

2012 - 2022

- Managed & initiated author printing, file formatting, & editorial review